SINEM CELENK

MBA | Marketing Professional



HELLO -

Enthusiastic about new trends, and consumer behaviors. Skilled in marketing, project communication, strategic management, thinking, and UX Design. Manages every step of the marketing project from initiation to closure. Enjoys conducting market research and finding new market opportunities. Expert external and internal communication Possesses broad management. creative experience with multiple brands such as L'Oréal Paris, Enterprise, Kotex, Kleenex, and Huggies.

CONTACT -



celenksinem@gmail.com



sinemcelenk



sinem.space

SKILLS & ABILITIES



CRM



Market Research & Analysis



Strategy & Planning



Marketing



Marketing



Public



Advertising



UX Design & Research



Marketing



Data Analysis



Creative Thinking



Management

References available upon request.

EXPERIENCE

MARKETING PROJECT MANAGER

Sparktank Franchise Marketing | June 2021- present

- Project management of franchise recruitment marketing campaigns, and website development projects.
- Developing and executing data-driven project plans.
- · Working with clients in various industries such as food & beverage, hospitality, education, retail and service.
- Responsible to build and maintain client relationships.

MARKETING SPECIALIST

Teskilat ICOM Advertising Agency | May 2018 - October 2018

- · Managed digital and conventional advertising campaigns for a global car rental company.
- · Organized workflow to meet team goals and deadlines.
- Managed creative team and client meetings, marketing campaigns, and budgets.

MARKETING SPECIALIST

A.N.D.B.R.A.N.D Advertising Agency | Nov 2017 - May 2018

- · Oversaw the creative team and managed marketing projects for various clients in the banking, oil & gas, security technologies industries.
- Prepared weekly working plans for the creative team and clients.
- · Managed external relationships with stakeholders.
- Tracked and reported on project milestones, duration to completion, and other key metrics.

PUBLIC RELATIONS SPECIALIST

Essance Istanbul Communication Consultancy | Feb 2015 -Nov 2016

- Developed corporate communications and PR Campaigns for global FMCG companies.
- · Assisted in developing competitive marketing strategies.
- Organized PR, Corporate Social Responsibility campaigns, Celebrity & Influencer management, and communication plans. Completed all the projects within an approved budget, timescale, and expected quality.

EDUCATION

MASTERS OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (MBA), MARKETING

University Canada West - Vancouver, Canada 2020 - 2022, 3.73/4

BRAINSTATION

UX Design Certificate - Vancouver, Canada 2022 - 2022

BACHELOR OF ARTS, PUBLIC RELATIONS AND ADVERTISING

Istanbul University - Istanbul, Turkey 2010 - 2014, 3.15/4